const quizDataHukisoku = [
    {
      question: "nosotros | ser",
      1: "es",
      2: "somos",
      3: "sois",
      correct: 2,
      display: "nosotros somos",
    },
    {
      question: "yo | estar",
      1: "estoy",
      2: "estás",
      3: "están",
      correct: 1,
      display: "yo estoy",
    },
    {
      question: "ustedes | poner",
      1: "pueden",
      2: "puede",
      3: "podéis",
      correct: 1,
      display: "ustedes pueden",
    },
    {
      question: "él | dar",
      1: "damos",
      2: "dais",
      3: "da",
      correct: 3,
      display: "él da",
    },
    {
      question: "yo | saber",
      1: "sabes",
      2: "sé",
      3: "sabemos",
      correct: 2,
      display: "yo sé",
    },
    {
      question: "yo | conocer",
      1: "conoce",
      2: "conozco",
      3: "conocéis",
      correct: 2,
      display: "yo conozco",
    },
    {
      question: "nosotras | querer",
      1: "quiere",
      2: "queremos",
      3: "quieren",
      correct: 2,
      display: "nosotras queremos",
    },
    {
      question: "vosotras | venir",
      1: "viene",
      2: "venimos",
      3: "venís",
      correct: 3,
      display: "vosotras venís",
    },
    {
      question: "tú | sentir",
      1: "sientes",
      2: "sienten",
      3: "sentís",
      correct: 1,
      display: "tú sientes",
    },
    {
      question: "yo | poner",
      1: "ponrd",
      2: "pongo",
      3: "pone",
      correct: 2,
      display: "yo pongo",
    },
  ];
 
  export { quizDataHukisoku };